not today
like actually this morning but this
morning it became although I reached on
rain boots come by that's my problem it
doesn't solve everybody's problem I'm
like why is it like it's outro rain
boots so fast and the ones except the
main Coover the people invest in they
can go through any pairs of kids either
find like a $15.00 and whatever I want a
system I want a system to be like this
kid needs this rain gear this snow gear
this and then you just like pass it on
to the next person like you know who the
next person is who who gets it
and it doesn't go through you know
Salvation Army and value build it to one
is just like anti-lgbt and the other one
is a for-profit company that prices
things way beyond what people who are
poor can afford them and any of them are
great sustainability but sharing the
sharing economy it I love the sharing
economy the not all parts the sharing
economy with the uber and airbnb ease
and stuff that are really just there's
been new word it's not really like green
washed they're like love washed like
look at us all sharing you're not
sharing your CEOs and people are getting
millions of dollars and the other people
aren't we're actually not really sharing
you're a platform and I know we can
create a all of the technology we can
create together the Netflix of apps like
that is what I want to exist already and
I am doing what I can
we're starting the idea cafe and it's
moving moving forward but I want it to
be here now like I want other people to
see the vision I can see and help me
create the Netflix of apps that we all
own together that is democratically run
and transparently run so we can have all
of those tools to run our own lives you
know also the last night cooked my own
oven when those meal prep delivery meal
things where they give you in it there's
so much packaging and it's in no way as
good as when I go to cohousing for
dinner labor wise cost wise
environmental wise any of it and I want
everybody to have a cozy type community
when everyone who wants one I'm not
gonna force community on anyone but
having the tools that make my life work
I don't know my just broken
like I can't just sit with yes yesterday
was an amazing day and I get to have a
day off I get to maybe not dismantle
capitalism today instead I'm like but
wait okay now I have the idea cafe I can
I can concentrate on my health I can
concentrate on my kid I can do
everything except this but I'm like no I
can't because capitals I'm still here
and everyone else doesn't even have what
I have and I have to get over that
it's gonna kill me so I will I'll get
over it and I'm gonna be kind to myself
today and allow calculus and Tremaine
per day one day more than one more day
clearly maybe more than one with it I
think the social media platforms I don't
know like people on Twitter or people on
Facebook like it's not it's not designed
it's not designed to find a social bit
but it's not designed to start a social
movement and I think myself included
before trying thought that like if you
had an idea on how to create something
in the world if you had a solution for
something it would just be easy to get
it out there like the world to be ready
for it in the world is ready the world
is ready for what I have to offer the
issues of course that I can't explain it
all in a nutshell but also like a lot of
people it's like that's too easy
no I don't want a peaceful way to do it
I want like violent revolution when do
we go in with the with the pitchforks
and take back everything from the rich
like we don't we just stop feeding them
we just stop and we invite them we
invite them to be part of what we're
gonna create but not as hierarchy down
just as a human being who owns things
happens to own more things and the rest
of us
but like creating a world that works for
everyone means we need it to work for
everyone including the rich and powerful
hmm that's not my that's not my go to
you should people to look out for though
so like my brain all day every day wants
to create solutions but the idea for the
solution not actually following through
on creating it which is how it's
supposed to be because they're supposed
to be people to create the ideas people
whose passion it is to do all of the
piece of this Florida not one person to
do it all that sounds horrible but to
have I can see that we can create the
technology for that to exist that like
to piecemeal something and sign assign
it to people that each piece is their
passion it's what they're looking for
and together it creates something
amazing is something technology can do
it's not that hard but it's creating a
technology and all of the amazing ideas
that are out there including this thing
I went to last night and a lot of people
who go through it either have a product
like a food product or a tech project
and the tech projects like don't stick
around because they don't have a
threshold of people to use them people
have an amazing tech idea but can't
market it and so creating the base the
thing that isn't like yes these are my
people and now I own them and now I get
to solve in my idea but like no we can
come up with ideas together and we know
that we are gonna use them because we
are the ones creating it but 10,000 of
us getting together can solve the food
crisis maybe not for 7.5 billion people
but for 10 thousand people and if we
solve like our individual food crisis we
figure out how to eat healthy delicious
food for less and less and less money
energy and time
who else is gonna want to not like
everyone's gonna want to be involved the
issue is we don't have the technology to
have those conversations on how do you
get 10,000 people together to create
food you can't you need like five people
together to create that and then they
have to sell it to the rest of them
which doesn't work which is why we need
the system to be able to anytime there
is an idea be able to easily recruit
people to work on it both a dedicated
force people who are going to do the
actual and gonna be like the board of
directors for the idea and then a larger
group of people that's willing to go
fund it and give ideas but understand
that their ideas are not it's not this
group's responsibility influent these
deals ideas it's your responsibility
implement your ideas like you can come
on board and implement them and come on
board and pull at them
alright I've been on for nearly ten
minutes I just wanted to come on and say
hi do my video for today and like I said
like oh and be kind to myself and allow
capitalism intervene not dismantle for
at least one more day but I did but
right before coming live wanted to
there's going to pick another time of
the week isn't the idea Cafe well the
idea Cafe is happening to come on this
channel and offer um it's gonna be some
point tomorrow I'm gonna pick a time
nobody come on and it's gonna stay at
that time over Friday and I'ma call it
fix the world Friday I'm gonna answer
people's questions on the system the
system we're creating together the
system that is in my head wanting to
come out to help create a world that
works for absolutely everybody where we
get to change this world and dismantle
capitalism and create a world that works
for everyone and I don't say that
lightly
I know how to do it I just need people
to ask questions that they understand
and they want to go on board because
that's how I can explain it but people
asking questions of like wait what about
this and what about this and what about
this I have the answers I just can't
give it to you in one big one Big Love
no elevator pitch here all right I will
see you tomorrow the better world is on
its way even if my body today doesn't
believe that that's not true
it knows a better world is on its way
it's gonna be brought to you by our
diversity or emotional diversity between
each other and on like good days and bad
days our mental diversity our physical
diversity and once it starts rolling
it's gonna happen much more rapidly than
even I I'm aware that it's gonna happen
I will see you tomorrow please like and
subscribe leave a little bell